https://lemur.duke.edu/engage/policies/

Merchandise Sales
General Tour (Private)
Little Lemurs (Children’s Tour)
General Tour (Public)
Premium Tours
Wild Workshops
Educational Programs + Camps
Events
General Tour (Self-Guided)
Internships
Amazon.com Wishlist — Send a Lemur a Present!
Merchandise Sales
General Tour (Private)
Little Lemurs (Children’s Tour)
General Tour (Public)
Premium Tours
Wild Workshops
Educational Programs + Camps
Events
General Tour (Self-Guided)
Internships
Amazon.com Wishlist — Send a Lemur a Present!
Refund policy
All online tour ticket and virtual package sales are final and non-refundable, and all purchases are specific to the date and time reserved. Purchases may be rescheduled to an available alternate date with no additional fee if purchaser requests at least 48 hours prior to their scheduled program.
Privacy policy
Duke Lemur Center and the Duke University Box Office are committed to protecting your online privacy. In general, you can visit our site without revealing any personal information.
However, you may be asked to provide personal information to gain access to some of our content and services, such as purchasing tour admission or items available for sale on this site. This information must be provided so that your purchase remains held under your name and can be located upon request.
We reserve the right, regardless of your mailing preferences, to contact you if there is a change, cancellation, or alteration has occurred to a tour, event, or product you have purchased through our offices.
This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as “Data” below) that may be collected by us on our site. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control.
Collection of data
Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information.
How we use cookies
Like many web sites, we may set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer’s hard drive when you visit them. This site uses aggregate data compiled by cookies to provide us with information about traffic to our site. Collecting this information does not allow us to personally identify you. If you modify your Web browser to reject cookies from our site, the functions and conveniences of our site may not work properly.
E-mail communications
Communication that you send to us via the e-mail links and forms on our site may be shared with a customer service representative or appropriate personnel to address your inquiry. We make every effort to respond in a timely fashion once communications are received, usually within three business days.
Because e-mail does not provide a completely secure and confidential means of communication, please do not use e-mail if you wish to keep your communication private. Instead, please call us directly at 919-401-7240 during business hours with your request.
Complaint process
If you have a complaint or problem, or if you believe your privacy rights have been violated, you may contact us at primate@duke.edu. Please indicate the reason for contacting us. We will assist you with your complaint or forward your email to the appropriate affiliate for response or resolution.
Overview: Tours + Educational Programs
Virtual Programs
Merchandise Sales
General Tour (Private)
Little Lemurs (Children’s Tour)
General Tour (Public)
Premium Tours
Wild Workshops
Educational Programs + Camps
Events
General Tour (Self-Guided)
Address: 3705 Erwin Road, Durham, NC 27705Phone: (919) 401-7240
